Guide to the Thomas Merton Center Records, 1962-2009 AIS.1982.19
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Second Deposit (1993), 1971-1993; II.
  - African National Congress (ANC) Constitutional Guidelines, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Children's Rights, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Children's Vigil, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Candlelight Children's Vigil, September 23, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - Center on War and the Child, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Coalition for Freedom South Africa, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Environment, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Earth Day Coalition, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - New People, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Press Statements/Articles, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Publications of Poverty, Racism, etc., 1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Wilkinsburg Arts Theatre (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Affordable Housing Coalition (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Housing Now!, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Housing Now! Rally, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Infant Mortality, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Pgh. Press, St. Clair Village Series, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Insight, May, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Food First News, 1982-1986 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Lay Religious Women (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Nambie Project, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - National Impact, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - South Africa Solidarity Network, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Race Relations Conference, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Results, Poverty/Hunger, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - The Right to Health Care Coalition, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - United National Information on Racial Discrimination, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Inventory of Org. Lit. (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Gay and Lesbian Rights Ordinances, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Three Rivers Community Fund, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Women, Misc., 1990 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Women's Rights/Family Issues (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Racism (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - YWCA Advocacy and Action Committee, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - 113 Mission Singers (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Coalition for District elections, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Lent Folder 183-88 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Pittsburgh Women's Church Files, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Prisoners of Conscience Sabbath, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - United States Committee for Justice to Lat. Am Political Prisoners, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - United Farm Workers, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - American, Arab. Anti-discrimination Committee, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Palestine Human Rights Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Palestinian Rights, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Palestine Solidarity Com., 1990 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Persian Gulf, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Pittsburgh, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - WV Peace Corps, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - "Limited" Nuclear War Strategy, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Peace Network, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - ACLU, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - A Race to Nowhere (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Education Action, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Merton Center 10th Anniversary, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Toxic Waste Dumping, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Citizens for Nursing Home Reform, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Mini-Kane Proposal, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Kane Hospital (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
  - U.S. Bishops Conference on Liberty and Justice for All, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Oakridge II (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Christian Peacemakers, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutional, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Center for the Study of Power and Peace, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - April Action for Peace, Jobs and Justice, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Nestles Boycott, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Labor Law Reform, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Agenda for Non-Collaboration, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Rush, Molly (Box 23, Folder 21-22)
  - Pittsburgh Foreign Policy Conference, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - World Hunger, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - World Hunger Information Kit (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Tax Resistance Pledge Fund for Life Mailings (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Nicaragua, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Articles on Women, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Retreat, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Nicaragua, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - National Pledge, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National Pledge Mailings, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - National Pledge (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - National Guard Information, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Handouts and Agenda (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Contadora, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Important Articles, Nicaragua, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Religious Task Force on Central America, 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Nora Astorga, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Central America, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Mercy Fund Grant, Spring 1986 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Material on Films, Books, Tapes, Photo Exhibits, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Witness for Peace, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Erie and Butler Pledge of Resistance (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Sister City Documents (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Fund for Life Organization Structure, Annual Report (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Understanding the Arms Race, Media Packet, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Nicaragua, 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Human Rights in Guatemala, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Misc. Central America, Magazines (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Civilian Victims of the U.S. Contra War, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Basta, National Journal, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Affirmative Action and Urban Issues, 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - American Indian Publication, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Anti-Abortion, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Center of Concern, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and Opinion, 1973-1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Dignity, (incomplete), 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Diocese of Pittsburgh, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Education Issues, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Issues, 1972-1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - International Women's Year Portfolio, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Meditations on Non-Violence (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Items on Corporate Responsibility, 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Gay Sources, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Periodicals, 1977-1982 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Profiles: Dignity Pittsburgh, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Religious Items, 1973, 1976, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Respect Life, 1974, 1976, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Sources of Guatemala, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam Items, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Women's Issues, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Coalition Close-Up, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Coalition for a New Military and Foreign Policy, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Critical Mass Energy Journal, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The Defense Monitor, 1973-1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Interchange, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Lucha Struggle, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Foreign Affairs, 1971, 1974, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Religious Publications, 1974, 1977, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Women's Publications, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - National Impact, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - National Organization for Women, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Near East Report, 1976-1981 (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
  - Network Quarterly, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - The Peacemaker, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Third Deposit (2000), 1977-2000; III.
  These records, mainly from the 1990s, document the center's opposition to Newt Gingrich's "Contract with America" legislation and welfare reform, reflecting the specifics of their impact in the Pittsburgh region. There are also alphabetical subject files covering a number of social and political issues, with a significant amount of material pertaining to peace advocacy and military issues such as nuclear waste. This series also contains the records of the Mobilization for Survival and Jobs with Peace initiatives of the 1980s, including correspondence and meeting minutes.
  - UN SSD II - Religious Task Force (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - War Toys (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Third Party Politics (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Toxic Waste (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Military Spending (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Trident Submarine (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - White Train (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Kim Dae Jung (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Impact (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Thomas Merton Center Board Members (Box 27, Folder 10-11)
  - Members, Speakers, Associates (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Kessler, Larry: Founder of Thomas Merton Center (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Tax Resistance (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - World Peace Tax Fund: Promotion and Publicity by the Thomas Merton Center (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Information on Memorials for Archbishop Oscar Romero (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - War Tax Refusers (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - A Correspondence with Congressman Doug Walgren (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Welfare Rights (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Veterans Fast for Peace (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Thomas Merton Center Sponsorship of Rev. Survil (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Chavez Memorial (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Peace Magazine (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - West German Peace Movement (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Social Action Directory (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Hunger Action Coalition (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Save the Family Conference, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Cuba Coalition, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - US-Soviet Relations, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Ernesto Cardenal Talk, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Isreali-Palestinian Art Show, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Building Peace (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Western Pennsylvania Rainbow Coalition, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Affirmative Action Strategy (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Mill Hunk Herald (Box 27, Folder 35-36)
  - Pittsburgh North Children's Essay Contest (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Pittsburgh Oral History Project (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - East/West Danes and Lithuanians Visit Pittsburgh (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Alliance For Progressive Action, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Co-Sponsored Events, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Merton Center Co-Sponsorships, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to Merton Center / to Rush, Molly, 1988-1991 (Box 28, Folder 4-4A)
  - Campaign-Pittsburgh Against Toxic Incinerators (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Ionic Crops, Bridgeville, Pa. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Power Co-Sponsorship, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Cease: Draft for Original Purpose (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Africa, June 16, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Peace and Justice Updates (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Children and the Arms Race, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - County Council Race (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Racial and Economic Justice Network, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Draft Board Selective Service - PA, Draft Resistance, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Mississippi Peace Cruise (Box 28, Folder 16-16A)
  - Cruise and Pershing II Missiles (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Thomas Merton Center Outreach Brochures (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Pittsburgh Committee for a Comprehensive Peace in the Middle East, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Persian Gulf War Articles and Notices (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Three Rivers Community Fund, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Three Rivers Fund, 1991-1996 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Three Rivers Fund, Surviving the Nineties, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Three Rivers Fund-Grant Applications, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Computer Calendar Planner Guide, 1980s-early 1990s (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Pittsburgh Cares Campaign, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Earth Day, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Computer Calendar Planner Guide, 1980s-1990s (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Pittsburgh Cares Campaign, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Earth Day, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Pittsburgh Weapons Connections, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Post-card Questionnaires Re: Nuclear Weapons, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Periodicals on Ethics (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - River City Campaign (RCC), 1983-1990 (Box 30, Folder 4-8)
  - Say Yes Campaign: Nuclear Freeze, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - River City Campaign (RCC), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 10-15)
  - Rockwell Shareholders Meetings, 1981-1984 (Box 30, Folder 16-19)
  - Rockwell Corp. Sales Reports, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Rockwell Shareholders Meetings, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Articles and Items Related to Arrests at Rockwell Corp., August 6, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Rockwell Arrests, March 31, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - River City Campaign (RCC) Leaflets (Box 30, Folder 24-25)
  - Forty Years After: Nuclear Protests, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - River City Campaign (RCC) Westinghouse and Nuclear Weapons, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1-5)
  - Ribbon Participants, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - The Other Westinghouse: Weapons and Waste, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - River City Campaign Flyers, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 9-10)
  - Pittsburgh Arms Pace Study Group Poetry, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - People's Defense Quorum, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Liane Norman Article, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - River City Campaign (RCC), 1981-1989 (Box 31, Folder 14-19)
  - SEI Flyers, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - USS Pittsburgh Submarine, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Westinghouse Arrests, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Articles on Westinghouse Arrests and Protests, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - River City Campaign (RCC) Retreat and Beginnings, Minutes, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Earth Net: RE Military Contracts and Spending (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Swords Into Plowshares: Nonviolent Direct Action for Disarmament (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - River City Campaign (RCC) Planning Retreat: Minutes, Winter 1987 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Westinghouse and Waste, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence with Westinghouse, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Department of Energy Facilities, 1987-1989 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - River City Campaign (RCC) Finance and Budget Report, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Items on RCC, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Issues of The New People, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - National Conference on Peacemaking and Conflict Resolution, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Social Action Calendar, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Thomas Merton Center Clusters-Organized by Area, St. Paul of the Cross Peace and Justice Items, 1987-1993 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Thomas Merton Center Cluster, 1980-1983 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Items on the Gang Piece Council, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Alliance for Progressive Action, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Social Action Calendar, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Tri-State Staff Reports: Board Letters, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Tri-State Conference on Steel, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Western Pennsylvania Campaign to Abolish Nuclear Weapons, 1998-2000 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Mississippi Peace Cruise (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Old Publications Donated by Shirley Nusser (TMC Member), Items date to, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Peace Justice and Ecology Directory, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Mothers in Prison, Children in Crisis Campaign, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Western Pennsylvania Coalition Against the Death the Death Penalty, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Tax Day-Penny Poll, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Great Peace March, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Expro-Coalition Program In Exploring Project on the Conditions of Peace, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Coalition Activity: Peace and Justice Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Grass Roots Organizing Packet, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Nailing Down the Peace Dividend, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Conference Coalition to Prevent Nuclear War, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Contract on Pittsburgh, Community Action Coalition, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Budget Campaign: Items on the Contract With America, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Contract With America, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Merton Center News RE: Contract With America, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Hearings on the Contract With America, April 28, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 8A-8C)
  - Citizens Budget Campaign: Left Off the Agenda Surveys, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Coalition for Economic Revitalization: Jobs for Peace, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Economic Conversion: A Conference For Labor, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Economic Conversion: Economic Adjustment Act, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Pittsburgh Peace Institute: Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Center for a Living Democracy, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Tri-State Conference on Steel: Jobs with Peace, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Keystone Research Institute, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - DC Days: Partners of TMC, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Citizen's Budget Campaign: Impact of Military Spending on Employment and Social Services, 1987-1989 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Citizen's Budget Campaign: Surveys on Military Spending (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Rainbow Coalition and Pittsburgh City Council, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Beyond Borders Conference, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Beyond Borders Conference-Finances, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Citizen's for Nursing Home Reform, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Committee to Improve Kane Hospital, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Mobilization for Survival, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Copy of Hammer of Justice: Molly Rush and the Plowshares Eight (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Issues of the Nuclear Register, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Christic Institute: Iran-Contra Affair, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - The Mill Hunk Herald, Summer 1988 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Pittsburgh Peace Network, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Issues of The Voice, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy (DMS) and DMX (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Good Friday Prayers for South Africa, undated (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Women in the Church, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Items on Aids, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Brother Patrick White, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Africa Peace Tour, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Letter for Lebanon, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Reflections from the Phillipines, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sanctuary in South America, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Peru Peace Network, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 8A-8C)
  - National Impact: Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Letters, 1987-1990 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Network ('A National Catholic Social Justice Lobby') Workshops (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Network Letters and Pamphlets, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Religious Outreach, Pittsburgh Peoples' Quincentennial (PPQ), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Prayer Service Announcements, 1982-1990 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Interfaith Prayer Services, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Network Members Phone Tree, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Network Elections Workshop, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Network Legislation Updates, 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Benjamin Linder Peace Tour, 1989-1991 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Items on PPQ, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Oscar Romero Events, 1988-1991 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Martyrs of El Salvador, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Americans for Safe Food, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - PPQ Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - State Welfare Initiatives, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Thomas Merton Center Mailing Lists (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Countdown to Eternity (Civil Rights and Dr. Martin Luther King JR. Material), 1995 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - New People meeting minutes and events, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Housing Now! Campaign, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - General Electric Boycott Information, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - River City Non-Violent Resistance Campaign (Flyers and Letters), 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - River City Flyers, late 1980s (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Rights Organizations, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Articles and Information Nuclear Facilities, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Fernald, Ohio Nuclear Plant, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Fernald, Ohio-Westinghouse and Nuclear Waste, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Waste in Ohio, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Waste and Department of Energy Articles, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Waste and Contamination in Hanford, Washington, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear Waste and Contamination in Idaho, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Nuclear Waste and Contamination in Savannah, Georgia, late 1989 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Nuclear Waste and Contamination in West Valley, New York (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear Waste and Contamination in New Mexico, 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Toxic Sites in Rocky Flats, Colorado, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Telephone Record Books, 1984-1988 (Box 35, Folder 15-19)
  - Humanitarian Aid Drive, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Nicaraguan Solidarity Network, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh/San Isidro Correspondance, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Sister City By-laws, San Isidro, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - San Isidro Photographs (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Storage File, late 1980s (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with San Isidro, 1992-1994 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Information on Nicaragua, El Salvador, Guatemala, and San Isidro (Nicaragua), 1990-1994 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Sister City Papers and Articles, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Sister City Articles, 1987-1990 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Sister City Information and Maps (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Sister City Events, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Sister City Donor Lists (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Sister City Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Northeast Sister City Meeting, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Hermanamientos (Brothers/Sisters), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Sister City Correspondence and Notes, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Sister City Proposal, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Garcia, Leonardo Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Pastors for Peace, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Latin America Items, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Central American Activists (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Nicaraguan Publications, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Nicaragua, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Nicaragua Fact Sheet Embassy, 1981-1987 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Religious Task Force on Central America, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Pastors for Peace in Cuba, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Voices for Haiti, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Pittsburgh-Guatemala Connection Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Pamphlets and Newsletters on Guatemala, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Guatemala Accords, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - El Salvador Reports, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Building New Hope in El Salvador, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Peru Solidarity, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Nicaragua Foreign Policy Issues, 1983-1993 (Box 36, Folder 35-36)
  - Human Rights Issues in Mexico, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Palestinian Concerns, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Israel and Nuclear Weapons, 1989-1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Reports on the Middles East, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Middle East Two State Solution Conference, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - National Organization on the Reformation of Marijuana Laws (NORML) Newsletters, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter on Pakistan in the Context of the Afghan War (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter on Namibia, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Native American Periodicals, 1985-1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Northern Ireland Newsletters, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Articles on Landmines, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - General Electric and Nuclear Weapons, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 11A-11B)
  - Greenham Common Women, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Hiroshima/Nagasaki Commemorations, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 13)